Guide to the George B. Post Architectural Records and Drawings Collection PR 53
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- New York Stock Exchange - New York, NY
  - Marble details of Broad St. front: plan through pediment; ink on linen (Box 307)
  - Broad St. front: plan at gallery floor; ink on linen, 1901-02-13 (Box 307)
  - Broad St. front: plan at board room floor; ink on linen (Box 307)
  - Broad St. front: plan at basement floor; ink on linen (Box 307)
  - New St. front: plan at board room floor; ink on linen, 1901-02-13 (Box 307)
  - New St. front: plan at gallery floor; ink on linen (Box 307)
  - Broad St. front: plan at basement floor showing granite; ink on linen (Box 307)
  - Marble details of New St. front: plan at club room floor; ink on linen (Box 307)
  - New St. front: plan at basement; ink on linen (Box 307)
  - Diagram showing jointing of pediment starter; ink on linen, 1901-08-15 (Box 306)
  - New St. entrance vestibule; ink on linen, 1901-06-01 (Box 306)
  - Detail of cellar floor; ink on linen, 1902-02-07 (Box 306)
  - Marble capping to wainscots & w.c. fronts in toilet rooms; ink on linen, 1902-01-30 (Box 306)
  - Lower part of section C-D, Broad St. elevation; ink on linen, 1901-03-18 (Box 306)
  - Iron gate between elevator hall & w.u. basement, Broad St. wing sub-basement 1 (Box 306)
  - Marble work: return of cornice, etc., west wall, Wall St. elevation; ink on linen, 1901-05-13 (Box 306)
  - Wall St. sidewalk & steps - bluestone; ink on linen, 1901-07-15 (Box 306)
  - Storm doors: Broad St. Anglo-American & vault entrances; graphite on trace (minor damage) (Box 73)
  - North elevation of secretary's room, bond room floor; graphite on trace, 1902-07-03 (Box 73)
  - East elevation of secretary's room, bond room floor; graphite on trace, 1902-07-03 (Box 73)
  - Plan of secretary's room, bond room floor; graphite on trace, 1902-07-03 (Box 73)
  - West elevation of secretary's room, bond room floor; graphite on trace, 1902-07-03 (Box 73)
  - Basins of fountain; graphite on trace, 1904-01-14 (Box 73)
  - Counters, desks & screens in clerks' work room, bond room floor; graphite on trace, 1902-08-25 (Box 73)
  - Furniture plan of secretary's office; ink & watercolor on trace, 1902-08-28 (Box 73)
  - Writing desks in board room; ink on trace, 1902-08-28 (Box 73)
  - Detail of bookcase & closet in stenographer's room; ink on trace, 1902-08-28 (Box 73)
  - Clothes press in clerks' work room, board room floor; ink on trace (Box 73)
  - Desks in board room rostrum; graphite on trace, 1902-12-18 (Box 73)
  - East elevation of president's room, bond room floor; graphite on trace, 1902-06-23 (Box 73)
  - Black board for bond room; graphite on trace, 1902-08-28 (Box 73)
  - Ice water tank; graphite on trace, 1903-12-08 (Box 73)
  - Plan of band stand; graphite on trace, 1903-03-25 (Box 73)
  - Cornice & balustrade, Wall St. elevation; graphite on trace, 1901-07-05 (Box 73)
  - Desk in treasurer's room; ink on trace, 1902-10-24 (Box 73)
  - Swing doors to entrance to board room from Commercial Cable Co.; ink on trace, 1903-02-26 (Box 73)
  - Furniture in secretary's ante room; ink on trace, 1902-08-28 (Box 73)
  - Plan of furniture in president's office; ink on trace, 1902-08-28 (Box 73)
  - Furniture for lobby, Broad St. entrance; ink on trace, 1902-08-28 (Box 73)
  - Furniture for board room floor; ink on trace, 1902-08-28 (Box 73)
  - Furniture in members' smoking room; ink on trace, 1902-08-28 (Box 73)
  - Furniture in clerk's work room, bond room floor; ink on trace, 1902-08-28 (Box 73)
  - Furniture for lobby, Broad St. entrance; ink on trace, 1902-08-28 (Box 73)
  - Furniture for bond room floor; ink on trace, 1902-08-28 (Box 73)
  - Furniture for committee rooms; ink on trace, 1902-08-28 (Box 73)
  - South elevation of president's room, bond room floor; graphite on trace, 1902-06-23 (Box 73)
  - North elevation of president's room, bond room floor; graphite on trace, 1902-06-23 (Box 73)
  - Plan of president's room, bond room floor; graphite on trace, 1902-06-23 (Box 73)
  - West elevation of president's room, bond room floor; graphite on trace, 1902-06-23 (Box 73)
  - Section thro' band stand telephone; graphite on trace, 1903-03-25 (Box 73)
  - Club floor, alteration to serving window; graphite on trace, 1902-09-22 (Box 73)
  - Club floor: details thro' cafe, bar, serving room & telephone booth; ink on linen, 1902-07-09 (Box 73)
  - Part attic plan: kitchen pantry & service room fixtures, luncheon club; ink on linen, 1902-08-02 (Box 73)
  - Trading posts showing collar; ink on linen, 1903-01-14 (Box 73)
  - Floor plan of Mortimer Building; ink on linen (Box 73)
  - Diagram of present floor; ink on linen (Box 73)
  - System of drainage for kitchen pantry & service room fixtures, luncheon club; ink on linen, 1902-08-02 (Box 73)
  - System of water supply; ink on linen, 1901-11-15 (Box 73)
  - Layout of barbers shop, basement floor; ink on linen, 1903-01-02 (Box 73)
  - Telephone booths around SW & NW corner pedestals in board room; ink on linen, 1902-06-02 (Box 73)
  - Trim for new doors & support for grille doors, sub-basement #1; ink on linen, 1903-10-10 (Box 73)
  - Section & upper plan, proposed alterations for Commercial Cable Building; ink on linen (Box 73)
  - Tailor's table; ink on linen (Box 73)
  - Raised platform east side of board room showing trench & space for future telephones; ink on linen, 1902-11-13 (Box 73)
  - Arrangement of telephone booths around piers, New St side of board room; ink on linen, 1902-05-02 (Box 73)
  - 1st story plan, proposed alterations for Commercial Cable Building; ink on linen; ink on linen (Box 73)
  - Heating duct in coat room of barber's shop, basement floor; ink on linen, 1903-01-15 (Box 73)
  - Pantry mezzanine between club & attic floors showing tiled walls; ink on linen, 1902-12-04 (Box 73)
  - Door from messenger's room to lobby of bond room; ink on linen, 1902-06-19 (Box 73)
  - Hat & coat racks & umbrella stands in hat & coat room, Broad St. entrance basement floor; ink on linen, 1902-07-22 (Box 73)
  - Rostrum in stock list committee room, bond room floor; ink on linen, 1902-09-08 (Box 73)
  - Detail of doors, board room floor; ink on linen, 1902-12-10 (Box 73)
  - Partitions & corridor entrance to Anglo-American Cable Co. room, basement floor; ink on linen, 1902-07-25 (Box 73)
  - Single isolated telephones in board room; ink on linen, 1902-05-02 (Box 73)
  - Archive room showing metallic filing cases; graphite on linen (Box 73)
  - Additional trench for Western Union office, basement floor; ink on linen, 1902-09-08 (Box 73)
  - Additional booths to single isolated telephones in board room; ink on linen, 1903-01-23 (Box 73)
  - Portion of sub-basement #1, plan showing Western Union; ink on linen (Box 73)
  - Wood & glass partition across corridor at column 88, attic floor; ink on linen, 1903-01-13 (Box 73)
  - Revised lobby & committee room, bond room floor; ink on linen, 1901-07-17 (Box 73)
  - Two closets for ticker company's rooms, attic floor; ink on linen, 1903-02-10 (Box 73)
  - Proposed layout of present file cases in archive room, bond room floor; ink on linen (Box 73)
  - Ducts for telegraph wires in Anglo-American Co. office; ink on linen, 1902-08-12 (Box 73)
  - Interior finish of 1st mezzanine stair hall, New St. wing; ink on linen, 1902-04-07 (Box 73)
  - Wood partitions for ladies toilet room, attic floor; ink on linen, 1902-10-14 (Box 73)
  - Oak closets for uniforms in room on club floor, Broad St. wing; ink on linen, 1903-02-04 (Box 73)
  - Part attic plan, addition to store room of luncheon club; ink on linen, 1903-09-30 (Box 73)
  - Revised arrangement of ticker companies room in attic floor; ink on linen, 1902-07-24 (Box 73)
  - Telephone booths in Broad St. annex, board room floor; ink on linen, 1902-07-16 (Box 73)
  - Proposed layout of present file cases in archive room, bond room floor; ink on linen, 1903-01-14 (Box 73)
  - Attic plan showing marble steps at door, between kitchen & stewarts office; ink on linen, 1902-09-12 (Box 73)
  - Extension to lobby in basement; ink on linen, 1902-03-11 (Box 73)
  - Iron gate in opening btwn lobby & elevator hall, Broad St. wing entrance; ink on linen, 1902-10-24 (Box 73)
  - Club floor dumbwaiters; ink on linen, 1902-05-26 (Box 73)
  - Buck plan for janitor's quarters; ink on linen, 1902-04-25 (Box 73)
  - Bulletin boards under rostrum, north wall; ink on linen, 1903-02-18 (Box 73)
  - Telephones in board room; ink on linen, 1902-05-02 (Box 73)
  - Additions in barber shop, basement; ink on linen, 1903-02-25 (Box 73)
  - Location of drainage pumps; ink on linen, 1902-08-18 (Box 73)
  - Plan of hat & coat racks & umbrella stands in coat room, club floor; ink on linen, 1903-02-07 (Box 73)
  - Plan of rostrum in board room showing position of furniture; ink on linen, 1903-01-14 (Box 73)
  - Shelf with hat & coat hooks, Mr. Bamford's room, 1st mezzanine Broad St. wing; ink on linen, 1903-02-03 (Box 73)
  - Location of signs for Western Union Co., Broad St. entrance; ink on linen, 1903-05-02 (Box 73)
  - Counters in hat & coat room, Broad St. entrance basement; ink on linen, 1902-05-08 (Box 73)
  - Door to vent duct in Anglo-American room, basement floor; ink on linen, 1902-09-09 (Box 73)
  - Dumbwaiter to bar, club floor; ink on linen, 1902-06-24 (Box 73)
  - Tank cradles; ink on linen, 1901-12-04 (Box 73)
  - Shelf with hat & coat hooks, room in sub-basement #1; ink on linen, 1903-02-03 (Box 73)
  - Elevator lobby off London Cable room, board room floor; ink on linen, 1902-04-07 (Box 73)
  - Lines on ground glass in doors to coupon booths; ink on linen, 1901-12-09 (Box 73)
  - Buck plan, sub-basement #2; ink on linen, 1902-06-10 (Box 73)
  - Bronze hand rails, stair from Commercial Cable to board room; ink on linen, 1903-01-28 (Box 73)
  - Cellar floor iron trap doors to furred ceiling, boiler & dynamo rooms; ink on linen, 1902-12-16 (Box 73)
  - Tables on rostrum; ink on linen, 1903-01-14 (Box 73)
  - Plan of typewriter's room showing hat & coat hooks; ink on linen, 1903-02-24 (Box 73)
  - Slop sink in superintendent's office, sub-basement #1; ink on linen, 1902-10-30 (Box 73)
  - Foundation plan; ink on linen (small format, not labeled) (Box 73)
  - Revised plan of grand stand for guest, opening day ceremonies; graphite on trace (damaged, unusable) (Box 309)
  - Marble work: panel, Wall St. side of board room near Broad St.; graphite on trace (damaged, unusable), 1901-12-11 (Box 309)
  - Marble work: blocks of marble for sculpture in pediment, Broad St. front; crayon on trace (damaged, unusable), 1901-07-26 (Box 309)
  - Layout for employees' hat & coat racks, sub-basement #1; graphite on trace (damaged, unusable), 1902-09-03 (Box 309)
  - South elevation of secretary's room, bond room floor; graphite on trace (damaged, unusable), 1902-07-03 (Box 309)
  - Jointing of large marble panels in board room; graphite on trace (damaged, unusable), 1902-03-04 (Box 309)
  - Counters in hat & coat room, Broad St. entrance basement; graphite on trace (damaged, unusable) (Box 309)
  - Doorway to New St. from corridor; ink on graphite (damaged, unusable), 1902-03-26 (Box 309)
  - Storm door, New St. basement entrance; graphite on trace (damaged, unusable), 1903-10-30 (Box 309)
  - New Street elevation, presentation drawing; ink wash on paper (damaged) (Box 309)
  - Basement plan, presentation drawing; ink on paper (Box 309)
  - Club floor, alcove of dining room; ink on linen, 1902-08-01 (Box 309)
  - Club floor dining room, plan of walls & ceiling; ink on linen, 1902-06-25 (Box 309)
  - Door to cut out boxes, Broad St. sub-basement #1; ink on linen, 1902-10-07 (Box 309)
  - Marble work: elevator lobby off London Cable room; ink on linen, 1901-11-29 (Box 309)
  - Plan at stairs to employees' locker room, sub-basement #1; ink on linen, 1901-08-03 (Box 309)
  - Additional steel cases for archive room, bond room floor; ink on linen, 1903-02-27 (Box 309)
  - Club floor, detail of mantel in cafe; ink on linen, 1902-08-01 (Box 309)
  - Club floor cafe plan of walls & ceiling; ink on linen, 1902-07-21 (Box 309)
  - Part attic floor showing doors in storage rooms; ink on linen, 1902-09-09 (Box 309)
  - Interior finish for janitor's quarters; ink on linen, 1902-04-25 (Box 309)
  - Metal moulding to cover joints between metal and plaster about vault in sub-basement #1; ink on linen, 1903-02-18 (Box 309)
  - Doors and finish in lobbies of bond room; ink on linen, 1902-05-20 (Box 309)
  - Doors for New St. wing, club floor; ink on linen, 1903-01-28 (Box 309)
  - Mail chutes on south wall in lobby, Broad St. entrance basement fl.; ink on linen, 1903-04-20 (Box 309)
  - Doors to cylinder shafts, Broad & New St. wings; ink on linen, 1902-02-11 (Box 309)
  - Doors to service elevator cylinder shaft, New St. wing; ink on linen, 1902-07-24 (Box 309)
  - Plan of lockers in superintendent's office, sub-basement #1; ink on linen, 1903-02-28 (Box 309)
  - Telephone booths, metal frame for names & numbers; ink on linen, 1903-02-05 (Box 309)
  - Doors to cylinder shafts; ink on linen, 1902-09-05 (Box 309)
  - New doors to cyliner shaft, Broad St. wing; ink on linen, 1902-09-29 (Box 309)
  - Doors to cylinder shaft, New St. wing; ink on linen, 1902-06-11 (Box 309)
  - Doors to cylinder shaft, New St. wing, 2nd mezz.; ink on linen, 1902-09-10 (Box 309)
  - Club dining room, panels over doors & mrror in mantel; ink on linen, 1902-12-24 (Box 309)
  - Club floor, hall to offiice, cafe, etc.; ink on linen, 1902-07-09 (Box 263)
  - System of drainage; ink on linen, 1901-08-15 (Box 263)
  - Wood frames and plate glass mirrors in toilet rooms; ink on linen, 1903-01-30 (Box 263)
  - Bond room floor: details for archive, ante & committee rooms, etc.; ink on linen, 1902-02-15 (Box 263)
  - Details of bond room; ink on linen, 1902-04-01 (Box 263)
  - Partition for lunch room, sub-basement; ink on linen, 1902-07-24 (Box 263)
  - Doors & trim at Broad St. wing entrance, New St. entrance to Western Union office; ink on linen, 1902-04-22 (Box 263)
  - Details of dining room, club floor; ink on linen, 1902-07-09 (Box 263)
  - Toilet rooms on 2nd, 3rd & 4th mezzanine, Wall St. wing; ink on linen, 1902-01-23 (Box 263)
  - Bond room floor corridors; ink on linen, 1902-02-14 (Box 263)
  - Bond room floor corridors; ink on linen, 1902-02-14 (Box 263)
  - Part club room floor plan, kitchen pantry & service room fixtures, luncheon club; ink on linen, 1902-08-02 (Box 263)
  - Marble work: New St. entrance lobby; ink on linen, 1901-09-03 (Box 263)
  - Club floor service room & corridor details; ink on linen, 1902-01-11 (Box 263)
  - Club floor service room & corridor elevations; ink on linen, 1902-01-13 (Box 263)
  - Finish of rooms, Broad St. wing stationary & bond room floors; ink on linen, 1902-01-11 (Box 263)
  - Mantel in dining room, club floor; ink on linen, 1902-08-15 (Box 263)
  - Pit in bond room floor; ink on linen, 1902-08-25 (Box 263)
  - Oak bookcase, 3rd mezz. Broad St. office of trustees gratuity fund; ink on linen (Box 263)
  - Committee rooms, bond room floor; ink on linen, 1902-07-16 (Box 263)
  - Attic floor: new scuttle, door & ladder, ticker co.'s room to vent space; ink on linen, 1902-10-10 (Box 263)
  - Club floor, proposed alteration to cafe; graphite on trace (damaged) (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: ceiling & pilasters, north end cafe; graphite on trace, 1911-08-24 (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: detail of wooden column; graphite on trace, 1911-07-18 (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: elevation of new opening in dining room; graphite on trace (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: elevation of new opening in dining room; graphite on trace (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: new serving kitchen, formerly east dining room; graphite on trace, with note, 1918-09-26 (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: east dining room; graphite on trace (Box 77)
  - Screens & doors btwn club dining room & service room; graphite on trace, with note (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: new serving kitchen exhaust duct & new pent house on roof for fan & motor; graphite on trace, 1918-08-16 (Box 77)
  - Proposed alterations to dining room; graphite on trace (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: north elevation of cafe & hall; graphite on trace, 1911-06-10 (Box 77)
  - Plan of bar; graphite on trace, 1911-05-08 (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: extension to east dining room; graphite on trace, 1911-06-10 (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: plan of cafe, new bar & hall; ink on linen, 1911-06-10 (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: ventilation of serving kitchen; graphite on linen, 1918-09-28 (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: ventilation of serving kitchen; graphite on linen (Box 77)
  - Plan showing enlarged room; graphite on linen
  - Alterations to luncheon club: panelling, cornice, shelves; blueprint on paper (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: wainscoting; blueprint on paper
  - Alterations to luncheon club: bar counter; blueprint on paper, 1911-08 (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: new serving kitchen, formally east dining room; blueprint on paper, 1918-08-05 (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: lunch table; blueprint on paper, 1911-08 (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: dining room, 7th fl.; blueprint on paper (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: plan of bar room; blueprint on paper, 2 copies, 1911-08-11 (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: layout of serving kitchen; blueprint on paper, with note (Box 77)
  - Support of water tank at 8th floor; blueprint on paper, 1903-12-09 (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: elevation & sections of wood screen; graphite on trace (folded, damaged), 1911-08-01 (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: elevation of bar, wood panelling; ink & watercolor on manila paper (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: new serving kitchen; gel-lithograph on linen, 1918-08-05 (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: sketch of floor plan; graphite on trace (Box 77)
  - Cast iron sump for surface water; aniline on paper (Box 77)
  - Alterations to luncheon club: small format sketches with notes; graphite on paper (11), 1911 (Box 77)
  - Heat & vent: board room floor; ferrogallic print on paper, 1900-12-06 (Box 77)
  - Heat & vent: bond room floor; ferrogallic print on paper, 1900-12-06 (Box 77)
  - Heat & vent: club room floor; ferrogallic print on paper, 1900-12-06 (Box 77)
  - Heat & vent: attic floor; ferrogallic print on paper, 1900-12-06 (Box 77)
  - Heat & vent: board room floor plan; aniline on linen, 1901-10-09 (Box OS-16)
  - Heat & vent: basement floor plan; aniline on linen, 1901-10-09 (Box OS-16)
  - Heat & vent: sub-basement #1 floor plan; aniline on linen, 1901-10-09 (Box OS-16)
  - Heat & vent: sub-basement #2 floor plan; aniline on linen, 1901-10-09 (Box OS-16)
  - Heat & vent: cellar floor plan; aniline on linen, 1901-10-09 (Box OS-16)
  - Heat & vent: gallery floor plan; aniline on linen, 1901-10-09 (Box OS-16)
  - Heat & vent: roof plan; aniline on linen with glued blueprint flap, 1901-10-09 (Box OS-16)
  - Heat & vent: attic floor plan; aniline on linen, 1901-10-09 (Box OS-16)
  - Heat & vent: 1st mezzanine floor plan; aniline on linen, 1901-10-09 (Box OS-16)
  - Heat & vent: 2nd mezzanine floor plan; aniline on linen, 1901-10-09 (Box OS-16)
  - Heat & vent: club room floor plan; aniline on linen, 1901-10-09 (Box OS-16)
  - Heat & vent: bond room floor plan; aniline on linen, 1901-10-09 (Box OS-16)
  - Heat & vent: 3rd mezzanine floor plan; aniline on linen, 1901-10-09 (Box OS-16)
  - Heat & vent: 4th mezzanine floor plan; aniline on linen, 1901-10-09 (Box OS-16)
  - Heat & vent: section through lower part of building looking east; aniline on linen, 1901-10-09 (Box OS-16)
  - Framing: deck house B or fan house; ink on linen, 1901-09-24 (Box 333)
  - Framing: girders GM 1-6; ink on linen, 1901-08-20 (Box 333)
  - Framing: Wall & New St. wing of G, H, I & J tiers; ink on linen, 1901-06-28 (Box 333)
  - Framing: bond room floor, K tier; ink on linen, 1901-08-30 (Box 333)
  - Framing: deck house A; ink on linen, 1901-08-12 (Box 333)
  - Framing: deck house D or janitors' quarters; ink on linen, 1901-08-27 (Box 333)
  - Framing: grillage plan; ink on linen (Box 333)
  - Framing: A tier or sub-basement & B tier of beams; ink on linen, 1901-06-12 (Box 333)
  - Framing: plan of C sub-basement #1 tier of beams; ink on linen, 1901-05-28 (Box 333)
  - Framing: detail of upright framing on New St.; ink on linen, 1901-11-20 (Box 333)
  - Framing: detail of upright framing on New St.; ink on linen, 1901-11-14 (Box 333)
  - Framing: columns BP 3-4 & south bulletin board framing; ink on linen, 1901-08-28 (Box 333)
  - Framing: bond room truss TA; ink on linen, 1901-08-26 (Box 333)
  - Framing: truss B, K tier or bond room floor; ink on linen, 1901-08-26 (Box 333)
  - Framing: truss D, K-tier or bond room floor; ink on linen, 1901-09-06 (Box 333)
  - Framing: bond room truss TD; ink on linen, 1901-09-07 (Box 333)
  - Framing: club room L tier; ink on linen, 1901-07-30 (Box 333)
  - Framing: attic or M tier of beams; ink on linen, 1901-08-19 (Box 333)
  - Framing: N tier or roof plan; ink on linen, 1901-09-07 (Box 333)
  - Framing: X tier, duct loft; ink on linen, 1901-09-17 (Box 333)
  - Framing: D or basement tier of beams; ink on linen, 1901-07-11 (Box 333)
  - Framing: E tier, board room floor; ink on linen, 1901-07-02 (Box 333)
  - Framing: gallery F tier; ink on linen, 1901-07-27 (Box 333)
  - Framing: G, H, I & J tiers Broad St wing; ink on linen, 1901-06-14 (Box 333)
  - Framing: columns BP1-2 & north bulletin board; ink on linen, 1901-08-30 (Box 333)
  - Framing: roof truss F; ink on linen, 1901-08-29 (Box 333)
  - Framing: trusses E; ink on linen, 1901-08-26 (Box 333)
  - Framing: hanging ceiling over board room; ink on linen, 1901-10-16 (Box 333)
  - Framing: truss C-K tier or bond room floor; ink on linen, 1901-09-06 (Box 333)
  - Framing: column bases; ink on linen, 1901-05-10 (Box 333)
  - Framing: braces for E tier; ink on linen, 1901-07-1 (Box 333)
  - Framing: columns L 53-60, 89, 90, 97 & 98; ink on linen, 1901-07-29 (Box 333)
  - Framing: plan of New St. vault & sidewalk; ink on linen, 1901-07-19 (Box 333)
  - Framing: girders G1-9; ink on linen, 1901-08-07 (Box 333)
  - Framing: M & N columns; ink on linen, 1901-08-06 (Box 333)
  - Framing: columns DE 36 & 35; ink on linen, 1901-06-19 (Box 333)
  - Framing: horizontal bracing btwn trusses; ink on linen, 1901-09-13 (Box 333)
  - Framing: columns 56-66; ink on linen, 1901-08-10 (Box 333)
  - Framing: columns L 61-88; ink on linen, 1901-08-03 (Box 333)
  - Framing: board room ceiling details; ink on linen, 1901-10-05 (Box 333)
  - Framing: vertical bracing X to N tier; ink on linen, 1901-11-18 (Box 333)
  - Framing: columns MN A3 to 50 & M 51-52; ink on linen, 1901-07-24 (Box 333)
  - Framing: skylight plan & gutter detail; ink on linen, 1901-10-02 (Box 333)
  - Framing: deck houses F & G; ink on linen, 1901-11-23 (Box 333)
  - Framing: deck house E; ink on linen, 1901-09-30 (Box 333)
  - Framing: columns DE 3a, 3b, 4a, 4b; ink on linen, 1901-06-01 (Box 333)
  - Framing: columns AC 1, 2, 5 & 6; ink on linen, 1901-05-17 (Box 333)
  - Framing: C tier girders; ink on linen, 1901-05-11 (Box 333)
  - Framing: columns MN 39-42; ink on linen, 1901-08-15 (Box 333)
  - Framing: girders GA2, GA4; ink on linen, 1901-06-21 (Box 333-A)
  - Framing: girders GA45-47; ink on linen, 1901-06-28 (Box 333-A)
  - Framing: columns ABC 27-32, CD 9-14, DE15; ink on linen, 1901-06-05 (Box 333-A)
  - Framing: skylight trusses TK6; ink on linen, 1901-09-17 (Box 333-A)
  - Framing: columns DE 16-32; ink on linen, 1901-05-14 (Box 333-A)
  - Framing: columns L70-87; ink on linen, 1901-08-02 (Box 333-A)